I'm in a seal show.
Today's goes to Cam Newton's hat.
Former NFL MVP Cam Newton was involved in a squabble at a youth football game.
I don't know.
I don't know the particulars around why.
Now Cam, who was 34, was fighting off two men.
And I mean, he was really like, they didn't take him down.
Like he stayed on his two feet.
But I think what kept him up there was the hat.
He went in there knowing something could go down.
So he said, let me put on my hat hat today.
Okay.
Because it feels like it could be a Montgomery brawl, August 5th type of situation.
So let me be prepared.
Because remember, that's another situation where a hat saved the day.
Today's goes to Black Entertainment Television for not letting their employees have a day off.
Roxy, one of the former hosts of 106 in Park, says,
remember when she and Terrence had a squabble?
Well, she said that wasn't real.
She said that was because they needed a vacation.
I just think it's so bugged that they had to create an entire scandal just to get a week off.
Like 106 in Park was not even a kind of show where they needed to be there every time.
You could have done a pre-record.
Like you couldn't let these little babies get some time off.
No vacation.
Years.
Three to four years with no days off?
Mm-mm.
We are...